JUAN URENA

GRAPHIC DESIGNER / WEB DEVELOPER

WWW.JUANLOVE.DESIGN



ABOUT ME

I'm a self-motivated professional with more than 5 years of experience in web development and graphic design. Extensive experience in developing projects from the requirements gathering phase to completion. High skilled in adobe software such as Illustrator, Photoshop, After Effects, Audition and InDesign. Familiar with HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP & mySQL, but also popular web building platforms ike Wordpress, Wix and Shopify.



CONTACT

Location:

La Verne, California

Phone:

626.531.1365

Email:

hello@juanlove.design

Website:

juanlove.design

Instagram:

juanlove.design



SKILLS

ADOBE SUITE

HTML | CSS | JS

PHP | MYSQL

VIDEO EDITING

GUITAR SKILLS



EXPERIENCES

FRONT - END DEV | DESIGNER

DATASLATE

2020 - CURRENT

Hired to design and code the front-end of their software application for the Mimyr project. Still apart of their team for projects I cannot currently disclose information of.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

ASURA

2019 - 2020

I designed their product packages, promotional materials, and website. I also responsible for video production, website maintence, and photography.

WEB DESIGNER / DEVELOPER

PVPZONE

2017 - CURRENT

All of pvpzone's videos, promos, merchandise, and their website was made by me. I also did the same for their sister company Jackie Bee. They still contact me for work.

APP DEV / WEB ADMIN

MT SIERRA COLLEGE

2015 - 2018

Started as a student in 2015 then hired within their LRC in later that year to then be promoted into their marketing team in 2016. I went from part-time to full-time when I earned my bachelors of arts degree in the Spring of 2017.



EDUCATION

MT SIERRA COLLEGE

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN GRAPHIC DESIGN

2015 - 2017

I took one year of courses at Citrus Community College then transfered to Mt Sierra College where I completed

my degree.



REFERENCE

OMAR PATEL | DATASLATE

Owner & Software Engineer
Contact Info: provided on request

EZEKIEL LAMOUREUX | ASURA

Director | Product Design Contact Info: provided on request